kevin.schmidlin@hotmail.com | Linkedin

## **Summary**

Driven and enthusiastic university student with proven analytical, critical, and creative thinking skills, specialising in Cyber Security and Forensics with a keen interest in Computer Science. Motivated to be part of a team and make a difference.

## **Experience**

Murdoch University 2021 – Present

Student Ambassador

- Delivered workshops, events and information sessions for prospective students, secondary school staff and parent groups
- · Developed leadership and communication skills
- · Gave university experience an edge and inspired others

**Woodside Energy 2021 – 2022** 

Cyber Security Intern

- · Assessed the risks to plant turnarounds should any or all digital services be denied
- · Determined any potential vulnerable or exploitable plant turnaround digital dependencies
- Discussed plant turnaround mitigation strategies

City Beach 2018 – 2021

Sales Assistant

- · Helped customers with questions, problems and complaints
- Continuously organised the store to be presentable and shoppable for customers, thereby improving store efficiency, reducing loss and increasing sales
- · Security tagged a wide range of products such as apparel, accessories and hardware

### **LEADing Lights CEWA**

2018

IT Support Technician

- Applied a logical approach to troubleshooting and resolving computer problems
- Built a chatbot with Microsoft OnA Maker
- · Entered and or updated data into internal records management system ServiceNow
- Total hours completed: 147

#### **Repair I.T Computer Services**

2017

Computer Repair Technician

- · Responded to all customer inquiries providing support and guidance
- Diagnosed any hardware, software and network issues that arose
- · Installed, repaired and upgraded customer PCs
- · Total hours completed: 127

#### **Education and Certifications**

Murdoch University 2019 – Present

Bachelor of Science, Major in Cyber Security and Forensics, Major in Computer Science

· Course GPA: 3.2/4.0

- Created effective and efficient relational database designs and systems
- Designed, wrote, and tested object-oriented programs that used self-designed and standard library abstract data structures
- Used various techniques to analyse and define business problems and opportunities, determining system requirements for modelling
- · Programming experience: C, C++, Flutter, Java, MATLAB, Python, SQL

ANZ 2021

Cyber@ANZ Program

· Completed practical task modules in social engineering investigation and digital investigation.

## **Murdoch University, Cisco**

2020

Architecture of the IoT

 Awarded a certificate of completion for successful completion of the Architecture of the IoT short course

# Google Digital Garage

2019

The Fundamentals of Digital Marketing

 Awarded a certificate of achievement for successful completion of the Fundamentals of Digital Marketing certification exam

YMCA 2018

Certificate II in Skills for Work and Vocational Pathways

· Attained a first-aid certificate

# North Metropolitan TAFE

2017

Certificate III in Screen and Media

- · Gained foundational skills in 2D and 3D animation
- · Demonstrated creative writing
- · Developed digital design skills

#### **Skills**

Active listening, communication, computer skills, customer service, interpersonal skills, leadership, management skills, problem-solving, time management and transferable skills.